all right ladies and gentlemen today is
a very special day and I wanted to do
something epic put up in a helicopter
land on top of a train get off with an
explosion and then reveal my pink
Lamborghini and I said you know what
this is actually something that goes a
lot deeper than that yeah I can make
something cool and entertaining and fun
but this is a deeper meaning of where we
are right now so this is exact same spot
known as Goya if you're from Florida
especially from Miami this is be like
one of the biggest car me areas in like
2018 2019 and I would put up here at be
here in my Hondas my Infinities and at
this very spot is where I did my first
car reveal or my first super car reveal
where I got my S550 and I upgraded to an
AUD R8 now fast forward 3 years later
and then here end up my own new Shon I
did it all by myself 24 years old I was
working at Duck and Donut 7 years ago
and I'm here so I want this video to
motivational I want to be inspirational
and instead of making it flashy and
crazy I rather make it real and
authentic to show you guys that you can
see in these clips that I have just
popped up where I was in the same exact
spot the same person just with a
different mindset and with the same
skill set just not using it to its full
potential this is the result of using
the same skill set every single day over
the course of the last 3 years and being
strategic with it so welcome to my we
got to eat the
Sher so what day is it it's currently
July
24th you guys probably won't see this
video
until October I'm buying the Bugatti
right now you [__] did I just
buy a Bugatti
D bro I just bought a Bugatti you know
what I'm paying for the Bugatti with the
$3,000 that
we what is that cover on the Bugatti
nothing not even the shipping bro
doesn't cover anything what is it I
might have hit it from you it's a little
obvious if you had to take a wild guess
what is it what's underneath there yeah
I still can't believe I bought this come
on take a wild guess wild swing I think
it's a Bugatti you think it's a Bugatti
is it about that time yeah yeah sorry
guys it's black and white oh that's
right cuz you can yeah it's going to be
black and white black and
white dude this color
[Music]
disgusting see first Bugatti I've ever
like sat in it's the one that I bought
it's crazy they're not they're not ready
for me in this [__] Bro they're are not
ready for me in this I going to say
something and say some words of Courage
but all I have to say is let him forget
that's all I got to
say congratulations Mr Al thank you
brother boy yeah the pink looks sick we
just [__] up the internet again oh the
streets aren't ready for me
now I heard checking for me checking on
me so I had to R up I got
mess
my My Success only made them EnV they
got upet I had to put all the Eagles in
check we can't MTI with the song what we
can't monetize with the song bro we just
bought a Bugatti we don't give a
[__] now as we make our way to the
Bugatti obviously this car is not
actually Peak you can see right here so
I actually gave my boy a chance to grap
the car he is a up and coming you know
entrepreneur and he wants to have his
own wrap shop and I said you know what
here here the keys I trust him he almost
[__] me up who would put the overlap
on top you're supposed to put this on
top of anything the car actually is
black it's like a black blue color so
this pretty sick and honestly every
since I got this car and I've been
putting my Instagram right here the
amount of women that I have been
receiving is actually insane I've been
receiving an influx of women like I have
never in my whole entire life I love the
outside of the car but kind of one of
the only cons is like the interior of
the car so like it has like a very
unique interior like girls girls what's
going on I'm doing a video come on come
on I I got to do a video ever since I
got the car I've been getting so many
girls oh sorry j come here hey I'll
check you guys later
bab love you baby hey get out of here
I'm doing a video bye thank you uh yeah
like I was telling you guys the interior
of the car is very unique it's very
different as you can see it's not like
one of those basic black on it's kind of
like one of these classic one of these
like old school interiors and I didn't
like it at the beginning but I actually
ended up falling in love with it because
you have the exposed black carbon all
over here in the steering wheel you
actually turn it off I don't know oh cuz
they had it on you have to have the dash
cam because you never know you got
people out here trying to do their own
little city [__] you know and this is
Miami and this is [__] Miami got I
think Miami is the number one city for
fraud or insurance fraud in the whole
entire country we have to fact check
that as you guys can see right here we
have the set and forget on the door
under this was the person that built the
car the guy that built the car was
someone named um what was it uh uh
Cristiano um probably like Cristiano
Ronaldo yeah uh um Cristiano Ronaldo or
something like that it's literally said
it under this right here
I don't know who the [__] that is so I
decided to just put set and forget over
it who the [__] is Cristiano Ronaldo
right one of the cool things kind of bad
things is I tried to color match the key
with the outside but you can't because
it's actually color match with the
inside so it's the leather on leather
and truthfully this is probably one of
the bigger cons of the car because if
you expect to pay 3 million for a car
you would expect a much more exclusive
and unique key yeah know you get this
piece of [__] voltswagon key which
actually cost $15 [__]
th000 well there goes $15 [__] th000
over here inside the glove box you
actually can see oh and by the way the
car is renting the car dude I I don't
know if you understand it' be actually
impossible to rent one of these cars
like it would cost you $30,000 a day you
multiply that times 30 how much is that
30 lost me at the first number yeah
right I think that's too much money for
us [__] can't fake this boys plate FX
Alex G something pretty cool that does
come with the car is going to be this
right here so this is like a little
Bugatti shiron booklet which kind of
teaches you how to use the whole entire
vehicle so you have a driving programs
and launch control section top speed
mode which is pretty [__] sick you
have the infotainment area you have the
center console which truthfully it is
pretty much Timeless and I know you guys
have probably heard this in the past
from other people but it is the truth
like this thing will probably you know
20 years still look futuristic because
it it pretty much is and it feels good
like the car the quality like it does
not feel cheap something that you
probably can't really see right now is
going to be this Center light right here
which is like the iconic sea of the
Bugatti which is super cool the only
thing I don't like about it is that when
you're driving you can't have it on it
only turns on when you're parked you're
going like 1 mph that's like a safety
hazard thing but I think it's super cool
and if somebody knows how to bypass that
and leave this on while you're driving
let me know that interior honestly is
really not much to it everything here
pretty much has its own unique function
just basic gauges that tell the climate
control and the pressure the actual
shifter feels good so I don't know if
you guys know but I literally had the
car for 2 weeks and I decided to be a
cool guy and I decided to want to be the
guy I was like you know what I'm going
to be the first guy ever to drift a pink
guy actually drift I know whistling
diesel did Donuts in it but in the snow
what's going on
as he wants a picture women and dudes oh
dude I get all types of dudes say what
say Miguel you like it it's not
mine I have to call the owner real quick
let me call him okay um I'm
kidding quick little B
yeah no no thank good I than good no no
no than good no no no
no actually just just SC
right I said one you said Miguel you
killed me with that like I was saying by
the way I feel like I'm one of like the
cool Bugatti owners like I feel like
Bugatti owners are douchebags you
probably would even let that like if you
weren't doing the video I would have
taken him for a spinner let him drive
honestly I really don't care at the end
day it's just a car honestly but like I
was saying for when I had the car in the
first 2 weeks literally I decided to be
the guy to do donuts in I'm like you
know what I want to do donuts in a pink
Bugatti so I saw that whistling diesel
did Donuts in the pink Bugatti but we
went all out and when we went all out we
[__] up two things
one I don't even want to say it cuz I
don't want it to like I don't want to
tamper with me we snapped the alternator
belt do I have a hair like is do I have
a hair that's standing up or no I no bro
you're good no yeah you sure cuz I
[__] I feel it okay whatever we did
the donuts and
Jesus get the [__]
out so we were doing a how many
interruptions are we going to have in
this [__] thing we're never going to
be able to finish this video Jesus man
Jesus Jesus so after doing the donuts I
snapped the belt to the alternator so
for all of my mechanics out there what
happens when you snap the belt to an
alternator the battery no longer charges
well I didn't know I snapped the belt
what ended up happening is the battery
died one day and I said ah [__] it died
in the middle of a music video with the
boy Kodak Black and when it died you
can't jump start it because it's a
lithium battery oh [__] oh [__] oh
[__] sounds like it's working no way
battery doesn't have more battery so
when I try and pop the front open up the
front over there it has a little it has
a little trick to it it has a little
trick oh open open it no
like seems open so when when we pop the
the frunk let me know what
else um yeah when we popped the frunk
and we were charging the battery uh we
realized that you can't charge the
battery because it's a lithium battery
so we actually ended up having to toll
the car having to Dolly it and the belt
by itself cost about like $2,000 cheap
but what happened is that the battery
died and you can't recharge a lithium
battery on a Bugatti so you have to
spend $35,000 on a Bugatti you have to
spend $25,000 in labor and you have to
finesse your way into getting the
battery and the belt for this car and
having the most gangster mechanic to do
it because the change this belt right
here is probably the craziest sh cuz
literally the belt is like in there
where we have one how many horsepower do
we have, 1500 this [__] has 1,500
horsepower Jesus so the belt is in there
and for you to change the belt after it
breaks you have to drop the engine I
found the most gangster Cuban mechanic
that you could possibly find change it
in 1 hour but he did not drop the engine
which is the key so it was $35,000 down
on just the battery and about $25,000 in
labor cuz you wanted to charge the C
prices and then after that we [__] up
something else very important which is a
down here the tires so as you can see
the tires are not in the best condition
so when you do donuts in second gear in
a Bugatti your tires are probably
spinning at like 7080 mph and then that
happens looks good to me right like I I
feel like we we've had worse the guys at
the Bugatti dealership they're telling
me bro you have to change the tires it's
going to be
$48,000 [__] that I'm not paying no
$488,000 sh go [__] tires what's
going on you guys are filming what's up
yes you know whose car that is or no no
I have no idea doing brother it's been
here all day and and we don't we don't
know whose car it is it's been there all
day keys are in there and everything is
it yours no you don't you don't know
whose car that
is it's literally been here all day I
don't know I don't know whose car this
is yeah we're going to have to call the
police department I'm going to call
right now cuz it might be stolen cuz
look look it doesn't have a license
plate it doesn't have a license plate
yeah I'm kidding it's it's my car you
don't have to call dude bro bro man
easy though yeah that was too easy yeah
I got you you know I go this this
couldn't be here like this trust me no
I'm kidding this is not my car bro I
don't know who this
is bro this this a $3 million car you
think I can do you think I could afford
this car probably yeah yeah I mean we're
just driving by uhhuh The Bu dropped us
off in the corner and we saw yeah right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay dude you got me once man you ain't
going to get me
again wow nice
oh there goes my
16 how many interruptions are we I
didn't want to interrupt you man oh no
trust me we haven't had any
interruptions today none n no
interruptions no you're not doing you're
not doing donuts you're not doing
burnouts here are you uh Donuts burnouts
burnouts no I don't I don't do that at
all we have a call people are doing
burnouts out here we're on a diet yeah
yeah hey you're on a diet sugarfree no
Donuts no Donuts no Donuts how do you
like how do you do it Donut oh come on
now you know who he really is no he's
the owner of Dunkin Donuts yeah I own
dunin Donuts he's the CEO
yeah yeah I'm not going to lie the
interrupted part K like I'm sorry I
don't mean I've interrupted no brother
we've only had 125 Interruption so
coming into the driver's side
now
honestly it's a [__] great car
dude it's honestly a [__] great car
dude it's like really good quality man
just makes you want to did I just break
the seat yo I just broke the seat look
at it look at
it little baby oil put it back in place
why would you say anything about baby
oil it's not like we have a trunk full
of it you have a trunk full of baby oil
I don't have a trunk I don't I don't
have a trunk I have a frunk oh and by
the way in here is probably something
that I will not unlock which is this
right here so if you guys step in here
you can see if we were to push this this
down this would pop up and now we are
handed the key that will unlock top
[__] speed you know that's kind of
ironic the key that unlocks the top
speed opens very slow top oh it's
getting a little fast when you have
beautiful women like the one that I have
your [__] goes up a lot faster than that
cuz you get more excited wouldn't you so
this key right here that opens very
slowly is the one that unlocks the top
speed in the car so you could pretty
much put it in here have the car on Turn
It Whatever way it decides to turn the
fast I've actually gone has been
207 and I don't understand how it goes
438 mph top speed when the dash is just
300 so that's a little bit of a
deceiving honestly from Bugatti it's
kind of a little false marketing and
they should check up on that oh and by
the way I'm going to rush to do this
video today because literally in 3 hours
this car is not going to look like this
it is going to have Christmas lights all
over it so I I wanted to make the car
Community mad just for being pink not
for being pink and putting Christmas
lights cuz that that would just be
disrespectful why would you want to
disrespect the car Community right so
you know what I decided to be a
gentleman and start off this video with
it pink and we're going to end off with
it in [__] Christmas lights so we are
inside of a $3 million car right now so
I pay like 3 million but like tax and
all that so I put down 1.2 million or
1.25 so a million and a qu and uh my
payments are about
47,000 or 48,000 insurance is 2K a month
plus gas and all like car wash I do all
the math always comes out to about like
50k a month and I'm not going to lie
I've had many different cars and I've
had many different experiences and none
are like this like none can compare to
what you're about to experience right
[Music]
now none I'm sorry none I've had two
twin turbo hurac pushing over 1200
horsepower I've had an SV I've had a 720
pushing almost 900 horsepower I had a
pizza pushing 800 horsepower I have a
ZO6 currently pushing 1,200 horsepower
and nothing feels like this and it it's
just the way it does the acceleration
how it
sounds the fact that you know you're in
a $3 million car it just it just doesn't
compare I'm not going to lie I'm not
going to Hype up Bugatti's ass right now
you know blow smoke up their ass but
they built an amazing
car I
personally don't think it's priced at $3
million truthfully I think there is a
lot of hype behind that because of the
top speed and it's the fastest car in
the
world I say this is maybe
uh $2 million car
2.2 but when you're in the three four5
million ah the doors don't even go up
you pay $3 million for a car and the
doors don't even go up kind of [__]
[__] is that you know so I I love it
the only thing that I hate about this
car is going to be the key so you guys
know the key is pathetic and it's small
and the stereo system the stereo system
in this car is absolutely ass literally
it it like don't even do it it's going
to you're going to get so ashamed of
yourself the fact that you even put
music in the car because it sounds
really bad so the real reason why I put
the Bugatti pink one because I don't
want to get a unique colored Bugatti I
definitely don't want to leave the
factory color because I felt like it was
too basic I did want to wrap it but I
wanted to wrap it in something different
like when somebody looks at it for them
to never forget I was going to do a
custom camouflage rap with the company
colors and I was going to do something
custom with the logos and a fade I'm
like I feel like I'm trying too hard
even though at the end of the day you
could really do whatever you want when
you're in a Bugatti because you're in a
Bugatti so randomly one of the guys on
the team was like yo why don't you just
do do it
pink and I looked at him I'm like wait
you're right why don't we just do it
pink cuz at the end of the day if
somebody doesn't like it if somebody
doesn't like the color of my Bugatti I
just say what color is your Bugatti and
there is a really good connection with
the pink not because of the actual [__]
you give to people it is literally the
same color of the Dunkin Donuts logo
that I used to work at so I said oh bro
it's a perfect connection and it's
actually worked out very well a lot of
people know the car and don't even know
me I don't even know how to take that so
something that I also really enjoy of
the car is going to be the way it
handles so
truthfully it is big or it feels big it
feels like it's very wide but you get
used to it very fast this thing handles
I say like a mix of a GT3 RS because it
feels planted to the ground and a mix of
a twin turbo Huracan because of the
speed and the acceleration you feel like
you could control the car my G23 RS I
[__] love it and I can take this
corner right now at 80 mph and not even
budge same thing with this you can take
it at 80 M hour and you feel like you're
on a yacht and it can control it and it
can go at 120 so it handles like a
Porsche in terms of like you know being
able to control everything but the
actual
speed is what makes it just feel
completely [__] different and I
wanted to straight pipe it I'm not even
going to lie see how it sound I've never
heard a straight pip
Bugatti but honestly I did not want to
test my patience with it in terms of how
durable it was going to be the car is
not in a warranty anymore
so not good one of the probably the
cooler features of it is when you're
going about like 110 120 and you slow
down and you hit the brakes the back
Wing pops up which is super [__] sick
I'm trying to get enough Runway right
now to do it but we're in the middle of
traffic hour
[Music]
look bro it looks so crazy when it goes
up because when it goes up the person
behind you sees the set and forget and
truthfully it's probably the biggest
Flex that I could ever have you don't
see the set and forget until I don't
bring the wing up which is kind of sick
and lately something that I've realizing
a lot which I guess it has like a
Snowball Effect to it is going to be how
your life changes when you own a Bugatti
in two different ways right change is in
a great benefit everybody respects you a
lot more everybody sees you as like a an
admirable person everybody listens to
your opinion a lot more than a normal
person and it's not because my opinion
means more it's just because since
you've acquired something that such a
small percentage of the population could
acquire you're just more respected and
that doesn't make me any different than
everybody else that just means that one
my priorities are different there's
people out there my I'm 24 years old
there's people out there my age that
probably have a lot more than I do or a
lot less than I do and they have
different priorities for me I want to
own a Bugatti at 24 I don't want to own
a Bugatti at 50 cuz I'm not going to
drive it the same I'm not going to
handle it the same I'm not going to
enjoy it the same it's not going to
affect my business the same when you see
a 24y old in a Bugatti like yo that guy
is on to some [__] [__] your value as
a person as a brand as a business goes
up incredibly because there is no doubt
now in what you do your competitors are
no longer competitors there want to be
versions of you with all due respect and
that's the great part of it right that's
the benefit of it you're seeing as one
of one because truthfully I really am
like I'm literally 24 years old with a
pink Bugatti self-made millionaire I
don't know anybody else there that has
done this to my
knowledge but then comes the bad [__]
the cons and that is that you start
getting Bugatti prices with [__] you
start getting taxed the other day this
guy over the phone I have a basketball
court in my backyard and he quoted me
over the phone $10,000 to repaint my
whole entire basketball court and I and
he was like okay just over the estimates
and the size and you're telling me it's
about 10,000 but I could could be a
little bit more if when I see it in
person if there's cracks and stuff like
that it won't go up that much I said
okay sure come over to the property
check it out and we'll see what the
final qut is and we get it done he goes
to my house he sees my driveway sees the
house and then sees
me the guy quoted me
$42,000 to repaint the basketball court
made up a bunch of [__] excuses that
now we have to refurbish the whole
entire court because there's cracks and
if we don't do it now the rain is going
to lift it up and I'm looking at this
guy like
dude just because I'm rich doesn't mean
I'm a [__] idiot like I get it you
want to hustle you want to make a little
bit more money because you see that I
have money that's not the right way to
do it the right way to do it is you give
me a great job and a great service and
I'm going to recommend you to other
people like me and that's how you get
your word that's how you get your money
you didn't get your money by [__] me
and a lot of people that encounter a
successful person they think that it's
only a once in A- lifetime opportunity
and they want to take advantage of that
that very moment with that person right
then and there but that's not the right
way on how you actually make money and
it kind of just pisses me off a little
bit because they want to take advantage
and I get it you know they don't want to
lose the opportunity but you're actually
losing the opportunity by trying to take
too much advantage of the person that
can potentially connect you with a
million other people so that's kind of
one of the cons like that's just a very
simple example like when I go to when I
went to a valet again it's [__] but
it's just like bro you could notice that
[__] changes I used to Valley at the
spot every time 100 bucks now since I'm
in a Bugatti $500 just to park a valley
in the front because it's more of a
liability for the valet even though that
I'm parking
it well it's also Miami for you can't
even lie to anybody out there that has
the opportunity to own a Bugatti or
aspires to own a Bugatti I would say yes
I would say get one I would say it's
going to change your the way you think
it's going to change the way your
business works it's going to change
everything around you
and it's definitely going to be worth it
100% there's not one second I don't
drive this car and it's not worth it and
it doesn't pay for itself it's just got
to have the [__] coones to come out
you know 1.2 million on a car and pay
50k a month on it that's a Trader
lifestyle for you that's the set and
forget lifestyle for you oh and by the
way we're going to feature somebody very
[__] cool in this Bugatti next week
he's the baddest [__] alive
right now
and all I can say is I'm ready for it if
he tries I'm G [__] him up oh I'mma [__]
him up oh don't let him try me I don't
know if I should be saying I'm looking
kind of scared of me saying that I can't
lie I hope he doesn't see that so ladies
and gentlemen all I can say is I
recommend the Bugatti 10 out of 10 if
you are not subscribed to the channel
make sure to subscribe right now we have
literally like nine more cars that I
have purchased and I want to show you
guys but only if you guys really want to
like I need the love from you guys we've
hit half a million subscribers literally
yesterday and it's crazy because all
this [__] just started as a dream and me
doing videos in my little closet in my
mom's house and now it's scaled to where
we are now so I appreciate all the love
I'm going to keep trying to give the
best quality and the best type of videos
for you guys as I possibly can trust me
this is only the beginning for the
Channel all you have to do is hit that
like And subscribe button I'll see you
guys in the next one and let's see how
these lights come out so I'm excited for
it we're going to do something unique
and shock a lot of people all around the
world haters
[Music]